Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  - Holt - Hom, 1927-1946 (Box 26, Folder 870)
  - Hook, 1919-1930 (Box 26, Folder 871)
  - Hoon, Paul, 1930-1931 (Box 26, Folder 872)
  - Hoop - Hor, 1916-1944 (Box 26, Folder 873)
  - Horst, Miles, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 874)
  - Horton, Charlotte E., 1931-1946 (Box 26, Folder 875)
  - Hosie, Laurence T., 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 876)
  - Hosk - How, 1916-1971 (Box 26, Folder 877)
  - Howard, James M., 1915-1944 (Box 26, Folder 878)
  - Howard, M. - Howd, 1927-1940 (Box 26, Folder 879)
  - Howd, Hadleigh, 1925-1941 (Box 26, Folder 880)
  - Howe, Arthur, 1914-1955 (Box 26, Folder 881)
  - Howe, H. - Hoy, 1915-1943 (Box 26, Folder 882)
  - Howell, Clarence V., 1937-1938 (Box 26, Folder 883)
  - Hoyt, Elton, 1915-1938 (Box 26, Folder 884)
  - Hoyt, J. - Hoyt, M., 1918-1919 (Box 26, Folder 885)
  - Hs, 1921-1934 (Box 26, Folder 886)
  - Hubbard, James DeWolfe, 1938-1940 (Box 26, Folder 887)
  - Hubbell, Harry M., 1944 (Box 26, Folder 888)
  - Hubert, George circa, 1917-1932 (Box 26, Folder 889)
  - Huckabee, Susie, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 890)
  - Huckabee, Weyman, Secretary of Foreign Students, 1927-1938 (Box 26, Folder 891)
  - Hul, 1917-1946 (Box 26, Folder 892)
  - Hume, Edward H., 1919-1955 (Box 26, Folder 893)
  - Hume, Robert, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 894)
  - Hume, Theodore circa, 1926-1938 (Box 26, Folder 895)
  - Hume, W. - Hump, 1938-1962 (Box 26, Folder 896)
  - Humphrey, Seldon, 1940-1944 (Box 27, Folder 897)
  - Hun - Huns, 1926-1933 (Box 27, Folder 898)
  - Hunter, circa L., 1920-1941 (Box 27, Folder 899)
  - Hunter, circa R. - Hur, 1920-1945 (Box 27, Folder 900)
  - Hurrey, Charles D. (Committee on Friendly Relations among Foreign Students), 1913-1938 (Box 27, Folder 901)
  - Hurry, M. - Hut, 1919-1945 (Box 27, Folder 902)
  - Hutcheson, Harold R., 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 903)
  - Hutchins, Francis, 1930-1957 (Box 27, Folder 904)
  - Hutchins, M. - Hutchins, W., 1916-1927 (Box 27, Folder 905)
  - Hutchinson, Gerald, 1944-1946 (Box 27, Folder 906)
  - Hutchinson, P. - Hutchinson, R., 1930-1933 (Box 27, Folder 907)
  - Hutton, Wallace circa, 1927-1940 (Box 27, Folder 908)
  - Hy - Hyde, 1916-1927 (Box 27, Folder 909)
  - Hyde, Theophilus R., 1916-1940 (Box 27, Folder 910)
  - Hyl - Hyn, 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 911)
  - Hyslop, Ralph, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 912)
  - Ib - Iv, 1915-1939 (Box 27, Folder 913)
  - Igler, Frederick B., 1931-1946 (Box 27, Folder 914)
  - Ingalls, Constance, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 915)
  - Ingalls, Harald, 1928-1945 (Box 27, Folder 916)
  - Irving, George, 1914-1919 (Box 27, Folder 917)
  - Irving, George, 1926-1938 (Box 27, Folder 918)
  - Itano, Harvey, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 919)
  - Ives, Charles, 1935-1945 (Box 27, Folder 920)
  - Ja, 1919-1973 (Box 27, Folder 921)
  - Jackson, Elmore, 1916-1939 (Box 27, Folder 922)
  - Jackson, Frances, 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 923)
  - Jacob, E. O., 1918-1938 (Box 27, Folder 924)
  - Jacob, Philip E., 1933-1938 (Box 27, Folder 925)
  - Jacobs, Earle E., 1955-1957 (Box 27, Folder 926)
  - Jacobson, Roy circa, 1916-1917 (Box 27, Folder 927)
  - James, Robert, 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 928)
  - Janeway, Charles, 1928-1944 (Box 28, Folder 929)
  - Je, 1914-1976 (Box 28, Folder 930)
  - Jefferson, Charles E., 1916-1917 (Box 28, Folder 931)
  - Jefferson, Edward F., 1913-1940 (Box 28, Folder 932)
  - Jenkins, Edwin, 1915-1933 (Box 28, Folder 933)
  - Jennings, Percy, 1928-1940 (Box 28, Folder 934)
  - Jo - Ju, 1916-1959 (Box 28, Folder 935)
  - Johns, Elizabeth, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 936)
  - Johnson, 1916-1973 (Box 28, Folder 937)
  - Johnson, F. B., 1916-1941 (Box 28, Folder 938)
  - Johnson, Robert L., 1916-1944 (Box 28, Folder 939)
  - Johnson, Ruth, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 940)
  - Johnston, O. T., 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 941)
  - Johnstone, Henry W., 1916-1926 (Box 28, Folder 942)
  - Jones, 1919-1974 (Box 28, Folder 943)
  - Jones, Esther Lloyd, 1930-1934 (Box 28, Folder 944)
  - Jones, Frederick S., 1914-1926 (Box 28, Folder 945)
  - Jones, Harold, 1933-1944 (Box 28, Folder 946)
  - Jones, Bishop Paul, 1925-1928 (Box 28, Folder 947)
  - Jones, Robert M., 1931 (Box 28, Folder 948)
  - Joyce, Jean, 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 949)
  - Judd, Walter, 1933-1940 (Box 28, Folder 950)
  - Julin, Bengt, 1936-1937 (Box 28, Folder 951)
  - K: Unidentified, 1916-1926 (Box 28, Folder 952)
  - Ka, 1916-1972 (Box 28, Folder 953)
  - Ke - Kee, 1926-1971 (Box 28, Folder 954)
  - Keeler, Martyn D., 1926-1946 (Box 28, Folder 955)
  - Keeler, Stephen E., 1939-1943 (Box 28, Folder 956)
  - Keeler, W. - Keene, 1926-1940 (Box 28, Folder 957)
  - Keith, Elmer D., 1925-1944 (Box 28, Folder 958)
  - Keith, R. - Kell, 1927-1972 (Box 28, Folder 959)
  - Kelley, Alden D., 1939-1945 (Box 28, Folder 960)
  - Kelley, Sidney G., 1914-1916 (Box 28, Folder 961)
  - Kellogg, Frederic B., 1937-1944 (Box 28, Folder 962)
  - Kellogg, Marion, 1941-1946 (Box 28, Folder 963)
  - Kelman, John, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 964)
  - Kelsey, Clarence H., 1915-1928 (Box 28, Folder 965)
  - Kelsey, Earl H, 1914-1926 (Box 28, Folder 966)
  - Kelsey, S. - Ken, 1915-1940 (Box 28, Folder 967)
  - Kendrick, Josephine M., 1938-1940 (Box 29, Folder 968)
  - Kendrick, W. - Kenn, 1926-1965 (Box 29, Folder 969)
  - Kennedy, circa Clark, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 970)
  - Kennedy, F. - Kenni, 1925-1933 (Box 29, Folder 971)
  - Kent, Charles F., 1913-1920 (Box 29, Folder 972)
  - Kent, Margaret, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 973)
  - Kent, Norton A., 1916-1941 (Box 29, Folder 974)
  - Kent, R. A. - Ker, 1917-1944 (Box 29, Folder 975)
  - Kershaw, Justin J., 1938 (Box 29, Folder 976)
  - Kerst - Kes, 1926-1930 (Box 29, Folder 977)
  - Ketcham, George F., 1926-1933 (Box 29, Folder 978)
  - Ketcham, H. - Ke, 1935-1962 (Box 29, Folder 979)
  - Khattar, Nasri, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 980)
  - Khattar, Nasri, 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 981)
  - Kidd, Joseph R., 1925-1940 (Box 29, Folder 982)
  - Kil, 1914-1928 (Box 29, Folder 983)
  - Kimball, Chase, 1936-1940 (Box 29, Folder 984)
  - Kimball, Clarence, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 985)
  - King, Douglas, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 986)
  - King, Edward, 1933-1940 (Box 29, Folder 987)
  - King, F. - King, H., 1943-1956 (Box 29, Folder 988)
  - King, Herbert, 1939-1944 (Box 29, Folder 989)
  - King, Mabel Houk, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 990)
  - King, Philip, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 991)
  - King, Richard R., Esq. Correspondence, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 992)
  - Kingan, Lois, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 993)
  - Kingman, Harry L., 1919-1940 (Box 29, Folder 994)
  - Kingsbury, 1915-1939 (Box 29, Folder 995)
  - Kinn - Kins, 1913-1962 (Box 29, Folder 996)
  - Kinsalving, Arthur L. ("Tui"), 1926-1946 (Box 29, Folder 997)
  - Kir - Kit, 1919-1969 (Box 29, Folder 998)
  - Kitchelt, Florence L. circa, 1928-1939 (Box 29, Folder 999)
  - Kitchelt, Richard, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 1000)
  - Kitchen, Wilmer J. (Box 29, Folder 1001)
    - 1926-1932
    - 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 1002)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 29, Folder 1003)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 1004)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 1005)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 1006)
    - 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 1007)
    - 1944-1971 (Box 30, Folder 1008)
  - Kl, 1917-1956 (Box 30, Folder 1009)
  - Kna, 1916-1961 (Box 30, Folder 1010)
  - Kneeland, George J., 1916 (Box 30, Folder 1011)
  - Knight, E. - Knight, F., 1919-1936 (Box 30, Folder 1012)
  - Knight, J. Stephen, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 1013)
  - Knight, K. - Knit, 1918-1946 (Box 30, Folder 1014)
  - Knoff, Gerald E., 1934-1938 (Box 30, Folder 1015)
  - Knol - Knox, 1916-1941 (Box 30, Folder 1016)
  - Ko - Kor, 1919-1945 (Box 30, Folder 1017)
  - Kotsching, Walter, 1926-1940 (Box 30, Folder 1018)
  - Kozaki, M., 1919 (Box 30, Folder 1019)
  - Kr - Kw, 1914-1974 (Box 30, Folder 1020)
  - La, 1915-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1021)
  - Lackland, George S., 1933-1940 (Box 30, Folder 1022)
  - Landram, Hugh H., 1926-1940 (Box 30, Folder 1023)
  - Langmuir, David B., 1930-1938 (Box 30, Folder 1024)
  - Lathrop, William G., 1925-1933 (Box 30, Folder 1025)
  - Latourette, Kenneth Scott, 1916-1946 (Box 30, Folder 1026)
  - Lauback, Frank, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 1027)
  - Laubenstein, Paul F., 1932-1940 (Box 30, Folder 1028)
  - Lawrence, William A., 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 1029)
  - Le, 1914-1962 (Box 30, Folder 1030)
  - Leavens, Dickson H., 1916-1943 (Box 30, Folder 1031)
  - Ledlie, John A., 1927 (Box 30, Folder 1032)
  - Lee, Armistead M., 1935-1939 (Box 30, Folder 1033)
  - Lee, Richard circa, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 1034)
  - Legate, Ray, 1925-1931 (Box 31, Folder 1035)
  - Leiper, Henry S., 1931-1956 (Box 31, Folder 1036)
  - Lenz, Friedrich W., 1939-1945 (Box 31, Folder 1037)
  - Lerrigo, Edith, 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 1038)
  - Lerrigo, Edith, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 1039)
  - Lewis, Helen, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 1040)
  - Lh - Li, 1915-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1041)
  - Libby, F. J., 1916-1936 (Box 31, Folder 1042)
  - Lilley, Frank, 1940-1949 (Box 31, Folder 1043)
  - Limbert, Paul, 1931-1943 (Box 31, Folder 1044)
  - Lin, Philip, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 1045)
  - Lindsay, Lewis P., 1927-1940 (Box 31, Folder 1046)
  - Link, Margaret M., 1925-1940 (Box 31, Folder 1047)
  - Lippencott, Benjamin, 1925-1928 (Box 31, Folder 1048)
  - Lipphard, William B., 1938-1940 (Box 31, Folder 1049)
  - Lippit, Henry, 1916 (Box 31, Folder 1050)
  - Lobenstine, Edwin circa, 1938-1946 (Box 31, Folder 1051)
  - Lockwood, Edward H., 1915-1926 (Box 31, Folder 1052)
  - Lockwood, Richard, 1938-1940 (Box 31, Folder 1053)
  - Lohmann, Carl A., 1930-1949 (Box 31, Folder 1054)
  - Lob - Lon, 1916-1946 (Box 31, Folder 1055)
  - Long, Charles H., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 1056)
  - Long, Royce R., 1919 (Box 31, Folder 1057)
  - Loo - Low, 1915-1959 (Box 31, Folder 1058)
  - Loram, Charles T., 1936-1944 (Box 31, Folder 1059)
  - Lovejoy, Allen P., 1916-1934 (Box 31, Folder 1060)
  - Lovejoy, Allen P., 1935-1944 (Box 32, Folder 1061)
  - Lovejoy, Frederick, 1925-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1062)
  - Lovell, Gilbert, 1920-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1063)
  - Lovell, Richard L., 1916-1921 (Box 32, Folder 1064)
  - Lovell, William N., 1933-1961 (Box 32, Folder 1065)
  - Lovett, A. Sydney, 1914-1932 (Box 32, Folder 1066)
  - Lovett, A. Sydney, 1933-1939 (Box 32, Folder 1067)
  - Lovett, A. Sydney, 1940-1971 (Box 32, Folder 1068)
  - Lowell, Deborah, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 1069)
  - Lu, 1916-1974 (Box 32, Folder 1070)
  - Luccock, Halford E., 1931-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1071)
  - Luce, Henry R., 1918-1956 (Box 32, Folder 1072)
  - Lull, Richard S., 1916-1933 (Box 32, Folder 1073)
  - Lum, Hermann A., 1916-1930 (Box 32, Folder 1074)
  - Lum, Hermann A., 1931-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1075)
  - Lummis, Martha, 1939-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1076)
  - Lute, Edward T., 1945-1946 (Box 32, Folder 1077)
  - Ly, 1916-1944 (Box 32, Folder 1078)
  - Lyon, D. Willard, 1913-1919 (Box 32, Folder 1079)
  - Mab - McC, 1913-1971 (Box 32, Folder 1080)
  - Macauley, A., 1918 (Box 32, Folder 1081)
  - McCabe, Donald, 1939-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1082)
  - MacCallum, J.A., 1938 (Box 32, Folder 1083)
  - McCance, Thomas, 1925-1926 (Box 32, Folder 1084)
  - McCance, William H., 1915-1941 (Box 32, Folder 1085)
  - McCa - McCu, 1913-1945 (Box 32, Folder 1086)
  - McClenahan, Robert S., 1919-1944 (Box 32, Folder 1087)
  - McClure, Archibald, 1915-1926 (Box 32, Folder 1088)
  - McClure, James circa K., 1915-1938 (Box 33, Folder 1089)
  - McCon - McCur, 1913-1945 (Box 33, Folder 1090)
  - McCorkel, Roy, 1936-1939 (Box 33, Folder 1091)
  - McCormick, Henry B., 1931-1940 (Box 33, Folder 1092)
  - McCormick, Vance circa, 1915-1932 (Box 33, Folder 1093)
  - McCormick, Vance circa, 1933-1945 (Box 33, Folder 1094)
  - McCoy, Charles Dana, 1925-1945 (Box 33, Folder 1095)
  - McCulloch, William P., 1916-1927 (Box 33, Folder 1096)
  - McCulloch, William P., 1928-1936 (Box 33, Folder 1097)
  - McCurdy, J. R., 1915-1945 (Box 33, Folder 1098)
  - MacD, 1916-1961 (Box 33, Folder 1099)
  - McDonald, J. W., 1926-1945 (Box 33, Folder 1100)
  - McDonnel, Hubert, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 1101)
  - McDowell, William, 1916-1918 (Box 33, Folder 1102)
  - McF - McG, 1916-1962 (Box 33, Folder 1103)
  - McGrath, Bernard J., 1932-1940 (Box 33, Folder 1104)
  - Mach - Maci, 1916-1946 (Box 33, Folder 1105)
  - McIlvride, Donald, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 1106)
  - Mack - Macko, 1918-1944 (Box 33, Folder 1107)
  - Mack, William J., 1935-1936 (Box 33, Folder 1108)
  - MacKay, John A., 1933-1940 (Box 33, Folder 1109)
  - McKee, Elmore M.
    - 1916-1920 (Box 33, Folder 1110)
    - 1920-1928 (Box 33, Folder 1111)
    - 1930-1938 (Box 33, Folder 1112)
    - 1939-1946 (Box 33, Folder 1113)
  - Mackie, Robert
    - 1934-1940 (Box 33, Folder 1114)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 1115)
    - 1944 (Box 33, Folder 1116)
    - 1945 (Box 33, Folder 1117)
  - McKim, Judson J., 1916-1925 (Box 33, Folder 1118)
  - McLa - McLe, 1915-1959 (Box 33, Folder 1119)
  - McLanahan, circa J., 1915-1931 (Box 33, Folder 1120)
  - MacLean, Rev. Burton A.
    - 1939-1949 (Box 34, Folder 1121)
    - Personal
      - 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1122)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 1123)
      - 1952 (Box 34, Folder 1124)
      - 1952 (Box 34, Folder 1125)
      - 1953 (Box 34, Folder 1126)
    - Grindstone, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 1127)
    - 1954 (Box 34, Folder 1128)
    - Personal, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 1129)
    - Personal, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 1130)
    - 1957 (Box 34, Folder 1131)
    - 1957 (Box 34, Folder 1132)
    - Personal, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 1133)
    - 1959-1965 (Box 34, Folder 1134)
  - McLennan, Donald R., Jr., 1939-1946 (Box 34, Folder 1135)
  - McMa - McMu, 1928-1938 (Box 34, Folder 1136)
  - McMillan, Neil, 1913-1926 (Box 34, Folder 1137)
  - McNa - McNu, 1916-1945 (Box 34, Folder 1138)
  - Maco - Macy, 1916-1939 (Box 34, Folder 1139)
  - Macouley, Alvin, 1917-1939 (Box 34, Folder 1140)
  - Mad - Mak, 1913-1962 (Box 34, Folder 1141)
  - Madison, Ward N., 1928-1939 (Box 34, Folder 1142)
  - Magee, John Gillespie, 1916-1946 (Box 34, Folder 1143)
  - Magill, Orrin R., 1928-1945 (Box 34, Folder 1144)
  - Maguire, Walter N., 1938-1960 (Box 35, Folder 1145)
  - Mahew, H.J., 1926-1938 (Box 35, Folder 1146)
  - Malcolm, Herbert L., 1916-1940 (Box 35, Folder 1147)
  - Male - Mall, 1919-1961 (Box 35, Folder 1148)
  - Mali, Harry J., 1919-1944 (Box 35, Folder 1149)
  - Malin, Pat, 1926-1937 (Box 35, Folder 1150)
  - The Edward Malley Co., 1935-1938 (Box 35, Folder 1151)
  - Mallon, H.N., 1916-1925 (Box 35, Folder 1152)
  - Mallory, Charles H., 1916-1946 (Box 35, Folder 1153)
  - Mallory, Robert, 1916-1920 (Box 35, Folder 1154)
  - Mand - Manu, 1918-1945 (Box 35, Folder 1155)
  - Manice, Edward, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 1156)
  - Manley, Felix, 1936-1939 (Box 35, Folder 1157)
  - Manter, John, 1933-1935 (Box 35, Folder 1158)
  - Marc - Mars, 1916-1960 (Box 35, Folder 1159)
  - Markley, Mary E., 1939-1943 (Box 35, Folder 1160)
  - Marling, Alfred E., 1914-1918 (Box 35, Folder 1161)
  - Marrel, L., 1925-1931 (Box 35, Folder 1162)
  - Marsh, A.M., 1914-1940 (Box 35, Folder 1163)
  - Marsh - Marst, 1916-1937 (Box 35, Folder 1164)
  - Mart - Marv, 1915-1962 (Box 35, Folder 1165)
  - Martin, Charles, 1945-1946 (Box 35, Folder 1166)
  - Martinez, Julita, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 1167)
  - Mas - Mat, 1916-1944 (Box 35, Folder 1168)
  - Mather, R.B., 1930-1946 (Box 35, Folder 1169)
  - Mathil, Simone, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 1170)
  - Matson, 1938-1956 (Box 35, Folder 1171)
  - Matson, Lillian T., 1936-1939 (Box 35, Folder 1172)
  - Matsumoto, Toru, 1938-1945 (Box 35, Folder 1173)
  - Matt - Matz, 1925-1959 (Box 35, Folder 1174)
  - Matthews, E.L., 1933-1934 (Box 35, Folder 1175)
  - Matthews, J.O. (Mrs.), 1944-1945 (Box 35, Folder 1176)
  - Maura - Maure, 1916-1946 (Box 35, Folder 1177)
  - Maurer, Oscar E., 1914-1938 (Box 35, Folder 1178)
  - Max - May, 1916-1943 (Box 35, Folder 1179)
  - Maxted, Ralph, 1925-1927 (Box 35, Folder 1180)
  - May, Alice, 1928-1934 (Box 35, Folder 1181)
  - Maylott, Worthy F., 1916-1933 (Box 36, Folder 1182)
  - Meac - Mead, 1916-1944 (Box 36, Folder 1183)
  - Meade, Parker Wright, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 1184)
  - Mead - Meek, 1919-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1185)
  - Meeks, Everett V., 1925-1946 (Box 36, Folder 1186)
  - Mei - Mel, 1920-1962 (Box 36, Folder 1187)
  - Meigs, Dwight R., 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 1188)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1940-1949 (Box 36, Folder 1189)
  - Menapace, Edward S., 1928-1941 (Box 36, Folder 1190)
  - Menapace, Robert, 1925-1940 (Box 36, Folder 1191)
  - Men - Mer, 1919-1946 (Box 36, Folder 1192)
  - Mendell, Clarence W., 1925-1939 (Box 36, Folder 1193)
  - Mendenhall, W.W., 1916-1941 (Box 36, Folder 1194)
  - Merc - Merg, 1913-1939 (Box 36, Folder 1195)
  - Merriam, George R., 1934-1935 (Box 36, Folder 1196)
  - Merriam, Thornton W., 1934-1936 (Box 36, Folder 1197)
  - Mer - Mes, 1926-1981 (Box 36, Folder 1198)
  - Merrill, Randolph Seaman, 1928-1930 (Box 36, Folder 1199)
  - Merrit, A.K. (Yale College Registrar), 1913-1926 (Box 36, Folder 1200)
  - Mer - Mey, 1916-1940 (Box 36, Folder 1201)
  - Metcalf, Mary Jane, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 1202)
  - Michel, Anthony L., 1925-1945 (Box 36, Folder 1203)
  - Michel, Frederick J., 1931-1941 (Box 36, Folder 1204)
  - Mick - Mih, 1933-1945 (Box 36, Folder 1205)
  - Micou, Paul, 1914-1918 (Box 36, Folder 1206)
  - Milbank, Jeremiah, 1939-1956 (Box 36, Folder 1207)
  - Mile - Mill, 1916-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1208)
  - Miller, Edward R., 1939 (Box 36, Folder 1209)
  - Miller, Francis P.
    - 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 1210)
    - 1916 (Box 36, Folder 1211)
    - 1917 (Box 36, Folder 1212)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 1213)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 36, Folder 1214)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 36, Folder 1215)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 36, Folder 1216)
  - Miller, H. - Miller, M., 1915-1972 (Box 36, Folder 1217)
  - Miller, Ogden D., 1933-1939 (Box 36, Folder 1218)
  - Miller, R. - Miller, T., 1931-1961 (Box 36, Folder 1219)
  - Miller, W.M., 1916-1945 (Box 37, Folder 1220)
  - Mill - Mino, 1920-1974 (Box 37, Folder 1221)
  - Minter, John, 1934-1945 (Box 37, Folder 1222)
  - Mir - Mix, 1933-1946 (Box 37, Folder 1223)
  - Mischler, Wendell W., 1915-1919 (Box 37, Folder 1224)
  - Mitchell, Sydney K., 1919-1943 (Box 37, Folder 1225)
  - Mod - Mon, 1916-1944 (Box 37, Folder 1226)
  - Montgomery, Robert N., 1934-1941 (Box 37, Folder 1227)
  - Moody, A. Gordon, 1914-1935 (Box 37, Folder 1228)
  - Moody, Paul, 1926-1939 (Box 37, Folder 1229)
  - Moody, William R., 1913-1918 (Box 37, Folder 1230)
  - Moody, William R., 1918-1939 (Box 37, Folder 1231)
  - Moon, Carroll M., 1944 (Box 37, Folder 1232)
  - Moon - Moor, 1916-1939 (Box 37, Folder 1233)
  - Moor, Arthur, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 1234)
  - Moore, G. circa, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 1235)
  - Moore, G. - Moore, J., 1920-1934 (Box 37, Folder 1236)
  - Moore, John, 1925-1945 (Box 37, Folder 1237)
  - Moore, Lawrence circa, 1931-1937 (Box 37, Folder 1238)
  - Moore, L. - Moore, W., 1926-1940 (Box 37, Folder 1239)
  - Moore, Webster circa, 1918-1927 (Box 37, Folder 1240)
  - Moors - Morg, 1919-1954 (Box 37, Folder 1241)
  - More - Morr, 1917-1962 (Box 37, Folder 1242)
  - Morehouse, Lyman A., 1933-1934 (Box 37, Folder 1243)
  - Moretti, Onorio, 1916-1920 (Box 37, Folder 1244)
  - Morgan, W. H., 1919-1938 (Box 37, Folder 1245)
  - Morris, Charles G., 1934-1943 (Box 37, Folder 1246)
  - Morris, D. - Morrissey, T., 1914-1976 (Box 37, Folder 1247)
  - Morris, E. P., 1916-1945 (Box 37, Folder 1248)
  - Morrow, Anne Faw, 1927-1939 (Box 37, Folder 1249)
  - Morr - Mors, 1918-1928 (Box 37, Folder 1250)
  - Morse, Richard circa, 1916-1939 (Box 37, Folder 1251)
  - Morton, Helen
    - 1933-1934 (Box 37, Folder 1252)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder 1253)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 37, Folder 1254)
    - 1939 (Box 37, Folder 1255)
    - 1940-1944 (Box 37, Folder 1256)
    - National Intercollegiate Christian Council, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 1257)
  - Morton, M. E., 1946 (Box 38, Folder 1258)
  - Mosc - Moss, 1914-1972 (Box 38, Folder 1259)
  - Mosher, Hugh G., 1917 (Box 38, Folder 1260)
  - Moss, Leslie B., 1933-1939 (Box 38, Folder 1261)
  - Moss - Mou, 1915-1931 (Box 38, Folder 1262)
  - Mott, John L., 1919-1920 (Box 38, Folder 1263)
  - Mott, Dr. John R.
    - 1914-1919 (Box 38, Folder 1264)
    - 1920-1928 (Box 38, Folder 1265)
    - 1930-1935 (Box 38, Folder 1266)
    - 1936-1938 (Box 38, Folder 1267)
    - International Missionary Council, 1939-1945 (Box 38, Folder 1268)
  - Mower, Helen M., 1939 (Box 38, Folder 1269)
  - Mud - Mul, 1919-1970 (Box 38, Folder 1270)
  - Mulligan, John M., 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1271)
  - Mulloy, John W., 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1272)
  - Mum - Mur, 1913-1962 (Box 38, Folder 1273)
  - Murray, John A., 1926-1928 (Box 38, Folder 1274)
  - Murr - Mus, 1925-1964 (Box 38, Folder 1275)
  - Murray, J. Lovell, 1913-1936 (Box 38, Folder 1276)
  - Murray, William D., 1913-1934 (Box 38, Folder 1277)
  - Musser, John M., 1939-1945 (Box 38, Folder 1278 - 1279)
  - Muste, A. J., 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 1280)
  - Myer - Mz, 1916-1970 (Box 38, Folder 1281)
  - Nag - Nap, 1918-1976 (Box 38, Folder 1282)
  - Nash, Norman, 1943-1946 (Box 38, Folder 1283)
  - Nason, John, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 1284)
  - Nason, Rachel circa, 1927-1928 (Box 38, Folder 1285)
  - Nau - Nay, 1919-1935 (Box 38, Folder 1286)
  - Neale, James B., 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 1287)
  - Neff, Frank, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 1288)
  - Neff, Ruth, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 1289)
  - Neitlich, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 1290)
  - Nelson, A. - Nelson, L., 1922-1934 (Box 38, Folder 1291)
  - Nelson, John Oliver, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 1292)
  - Nelson, Roger, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 1293)
  - Nesbit, Ralph B., 1918-1934 (Box 38, Folder 1294)
  - Nestigen, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 1295)
  - Nettletor, George H., 1921-1945 (Box 38, Folder 1296)
  - Nett - Newc, 1916-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1297)
  - Newell, Arthur F., 1919-1920 (Box 38, Folder 1298)
  - Newl - Newt, 1925-1944 (Box 38, Folder 1299)
  - Newton, Howard, 1916-1933 (Box 38, Folder 1300)
  - Newton, Ray, 1935-1940 (Box 39, Folder 1301)
  - Nicholls, M.circa (Bridgeport YMCA), 1921 (Box 39, Folder 1302)
  - Nichols, A. - Nichols, R., 1916-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1303)
  - Nichols, James H., 1936-1944 (Box 39, Folder 1304)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1925-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1305)
  - Nilson, Lillian, 1928-1936 (Box 39, Folder 1306)
  - Nilssen, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 1307)
  - Noble, circa - Noble, H., 1946-1955 (Box 39, Folder 1308)
  - Noble, circa circa (Williams College YMCA), 1921 (Box 39, Folder 1309)
  - Noble, Grant, 1930-1940 (Box 39, Folder 1310)
  - Noble, Nathaniel, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 1311)
  - Nol - Noy, 1916-1960 (Box 39, Folder 1312)
  - Norris, G. R., 1938 (Box 39, Folder 1313)
  - Norris, Margaret S., 1933-1944 (Box 39, Folder 1314)
  - North, Donald G., 1927-1941 (Box 39, Folder 1315)
  - Northrop, Filmer, 1927-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1316)
  - Norton, D. - Norton, W., 1916-1946 (Box 39, Folder 1317)
  - Noyes, Morgan, 1913-1946 (Box 39, Folder 1318 - 1319)
  - Nugent, Gordon W., 1944 (Box 39, Folder 1320)
  - Nya - Nys, 1931-1944 (Box 39, Folder 1321)
  - Oa, 1936-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1322)
  - Ob - Od, 1916-1961 (Box 39, Folder 1323)
  - Ober, circa K., 1915-1920 (Box 39, Folder 1324)
  - Odell, Floyd, 1938-1940 (Box 39, Folder 1325)
  - Og - Ol, 1914-1946 (Box 39, Folder 1326)
  - Olmstead, Frank I., 1920-1940 (Box 39, Folder 1327)
  - On - Or, 1916-1945 (Box 40, Folder 1328)
  - Orrick, A. Downey, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 1329)
  - Or - Os, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 1330)
  - Osbourn, circa S., 1916-1926 (Box 40, Folder 1331)
  - Osg, 1917 (Box 40, Folder 1332)
  - Ostrander, Harry J., 1927-1945 (Box 40, Folder 1333)
  - Osw - Ow, 1914-1955 (Box 40, Folder 1334)
  - Owen, David, 1921-1931 (Box 40, Folder 1335)
  - Owen, G. - Owen, L., 1934-1939 (Box 40, Folder 1336)
  - Pa - Pac, 1914-1940 (Box 40, Folder 1337)